<resources>
    <string name="app_name">5 for 5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_manage_contacts">Manage Contacts</string>
    <string name="button_manage_contacts">manage contacts</string>
    <string name="button_manage_messages">manage messages</string>
    <string name="button_settings">settings</string>
    <string name="button_quick_start_guide">quick start guide</string>
    <string name="button_create_message">create new message</string>
    <string name="button_save">save</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_phone_book">PhoneBook</string>
    <string name="title_activity_quick_start">QuickStart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_quick_start_fragment">QuickStartFragment</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="page_one_title">Welcome</string>
    <string name="page_one_body_top">Welcome to Five for Five - and thank you for helping to
        test this app! Over the next few screens, you\'ll see what this app is about
        and how easy it is to get everything up and going.</string>
    <string name="page_one_body_bottom">Swipe to continue, and hit back at any time to skip the explanation. You can always read this later.</string>
    <string name="page_two_title">What is this about</string>
    <string name="page_two_body_top">A survey in September 2015 (AAU)
        found that \23 percent of female undergrads have reported experiencing sexual assault since enrolling in
        college.\ Another survey (NIJ) found that 1 in 6  American adult women has been the victim of an attempted or
        completed rape in her lifetime. This means that fewer than 4 out of 5 women
        live out their lives unmolested.</string>
    <string name="page_two_middle">Four out five isn\'t good enough. We need to push for five.</string>
    <string name="page_two_body_bottom">This app is designed to turn your phone into a discreet trigger you can use to alert your
        friends in seconds. Just push your power button three times and
        you\'ve sent a message to a few close people in your life who might be able to help. Some suggestions for when you might want to use this app:
        Before heading home at night, alert your group to help you if you don\'t check back in;
        If you see something or someone that seems off, for whatever reason, quietly alert your friends;
        If you get pulled over and something seems off, discretely let your friends know what\'s happening.
        Let\'s get started!</string>
    <string name="page_three_title">Make a Contact Group</string>
    <string name="page_three_body_top">First, you\'ll want to set up a group of people you want to alert.
        Your groups can include as many or as few contacts as you\'d like. Keep in mind that messages are sent
        individually to each contact, so each person will assume you are sending them a personal text.
        This makes it more likely for your contacts to respond and help.</string>
    <string name="page_three_body_bottom">To get started, click Manage Contacts from the Welcome screen.
        You\'ll have one group by default, and can add as many additional groups as you like. We\'ll talk
        about choosing a default alert group in a few screens.</string>
    <string name="page_four_title">Make a Message (or two)</string>
    <string name="page_four_body_top">Next, you\'ll want to set up a message that explains what\'s going on.
        You can make as many messages as you want, so consider creating an SOS message as well as one to
        let everyone know you\'re OK. It\'s even faster than checking in on Facebook.</string>
    <string name="page_four_body_bottom">To get started, click Messages from the Welcome screen.
        You\'ll have one message by default, which you can edit or delete as you like.</string>
    <string name="page_five_title">Set your defaults</string>
    <string name="page_five_body_top">You can control which message gets sent to which group in the
        Settings screen. This is where you\'ll specify how many clicks will trigger the alarm, which
        message you want to send, and which group to notify. If you want to send a different message
        to a different group, just click the big \"sound the alarm!\" button
        on the home screen.</string>
    <string name="page_five_body_bottom">Additional settings still under development:
        Setting a time delay, so the alert message is only sent if you don\'t disarm it;
        Including your location in the SOS message;
        Starting audio recording when the alert is triggered;
        Status updates to friends who also have the app via push notifications.
        All suggestions, comments, and (constructive) criticism appreciated. Stay safe!</string>
    <string name="spinner_prompt">Choose a default message</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_alarm">TestAlarm</string>
    <string name="title_activity_delayed_alarm">DelayedAlarm</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sound_the_alarm">SoundTheAlarm</string>
</resources>